Charming Christmas is a tv movie, romance, drama film directed by Craig Pryce.
Meredith Rossman has made Rossman's Department store her entire
life, not leaving any time for Christmas or romance.
But when she is roped into donning the store's antique Mrs.
Claus outfit to play Mrs.
Claus at Rossman's famous Santaville, her life takes some unexpected turns.
Through the help of the suit and the charming store Santa, Nick, Meredith rekindles her love of
Christmas, the store, their employees and possibly even begins a new love with Nick.
Meredith Rossman, played by Julie Benz.
Nick, played by David Sutcliffe.
Harold Rossman, played by Bruce Gray.
Cheryl Rossman, played by Catherine McNally.
Olivia Todd, played by Vanessa Matsui.
Jessie Derringer, played by Ashley Leggat.
Many Christmas stories have been adapted to feature films and TV specials,
and have been broadcast and repeated many times on television.
Since the popularization of home video in the 1980s, these films are sold
and re-sold every year during the holiday shopping season.
Many television networks, film studios, and production companies, such as cable television channels Hallmark and Lifetime, produce and
release new Christmas-themed films every year during or around December, all with variations of similar plots and themes.
Additionally, films revolving around the Nativity story of Christmas are regularly
produced such as The Nativity Story (2006) and The Star (2017).
One film that has become the flashpoint for "Is this a Christmas movie or not?" debates is Die Hard (1988), with some viewing the film as a
Christmas movie intertwined with an action genre setting or a film that is simply set around the Christmas and holiday season.
The tone is emotional.